soundsonline.com 2017-12-03

# EastWest Privacy Policy

We at SOUNDS ONLINE understand that making purchases online involves a great deal of trust on your part; we take that trust seriously, and make it our highest priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the information you provide us, such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. As a visitor to our web site, you have the right to understand our privacy practices prior to providing us with any of your information. 

### **What Information We Collect**

SOUNDS ONLINE only collects information that you voluntarily provide to us. We use collected information for marketing and advertising products and services. 

### **How We Use Your Information**

SOUNDS ONLINE uses your information only for the purpose of responding to and fulfilling your requests for products and services. 

### **Who We Share Your Information With**

No one. We NEVER share, sell or rent the information you supply to ANYONE. 

### **How We Protect Your Information**

Our secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard, and amongst the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts ALL of your personal information including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. 

### **Information Collected about you**

SOUNDS ONLINE collects information about you that you specifically and voluntarily provide, including information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name, phone number, or e-mail address. Although you are required to register in order to use some of the transaction tools, many areas of the SOUNDS ONLINE site can be accessed without providing any information. On all pages that collect information, we specifically describe what information is required in order to provide you with the product or service you have requested. SOUNDS ONLINE collects information when you: 

  * Make a purchase
  * Contact a phone sales representative
  * Are contacted by a phone sales representative
  * Participate in a survey

SOUNDS ONLINE collects your unique e-mail address and password when you register at our web site. 

### **Purchase information**

SOUNDS ONLINE collects the billing address of the credit card that is used to purchase products. We will also collect credit card information including card number, card type, cardholder name, and expiration date, in order to bill you for purchases made through SOUNDS ONLINE. 

### **Surveys**

Occasionally, SOUNDS ONLINE may offer our customers and site visitors an opportunity to participate in a survey. Information collected by SOUNDS ONLINE when you participate in a survey, may include your full name, phone number, e-mail address and street address. The information is NEVER shared with any third party. 

### **Other information we collect**

Session ID: Upon visiting our site we will assign you a unique Session ID in the form of a "cookie", a cookie is a piece of information that a web site sends to a browser. If you are using one of the leading Internet browsers, this information will only be stored temporarily in memory and not the hard drive. This is used to facilitate your shopping experience and order, keep track of your shopping basket during your visit, help diagnose problems with our server, and administer our Web site. Upon exiting your browser this temporary Session ID is then discarded. By default all web server log files capture IP address however we use your IP to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

### **E-Mail notifications**

As a customer, and visitor to SOUNDS ONLINE, you can receive e-mails about electronic catalogs, special promotions, surveys or other opportunities at SOUNDS ONLINE. We always provide a link in each e-mail to enable you to remove your email address if you don't wish to receive these e-mail notifications. 

### **Responses to your questions or suggestions**

We will use your e-mail address or telephone number to respond when you submit a question or suggestion, or request assistance with reviewing an order status, loggin into or accessing your SOUNDS ONLINE account. 

### **Changes to the SOUNDS ONLINE Privacy Statement**

SOUNDS ONLINE reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Statement any time and for any reason. If you have questions about our Privacy Statement, please e-mail us.
